A Guide to the R. Bruce Merrifield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA415
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Manuscripts and Publications, 5
  - "SPPS: Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Stewart and Young (Box 358, Folder 2233)
  - Stenflo (Box 358, Folder 2234)
  - Stewart, John Morrow (Box 358, Folder 2235)
  - Stewart and Young, 2nd Edition (Box 359, Folder 2236)
  - Stoffel, PNAS (Box 359, Folder 2237)
  - "Strepogenin Activity of Synthetic Peptides Related to Oxytocin" by Merrifield et al. (Box 359, Folder 2238)
  - "Structure-Function Studies on the ACTH Family of Hormones" by Draper, 1974 (Box 359, Folder 2239-2240)
  - "Studies on Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis" by Marshall, 1966 (Box 359, Folder 2241)
  - "Studies on Solid-Phase Peptide Synthesis: The Synthesis of Glucagon" by Mojsov, 1978 (Box 360, Folder 2242)
  - "Studies on the Reaction Mechanism of the Catalytic Subunit of Calf Thymus Cyclic AMP-Dependent Protein Kinase Using Synthetic Polypeptide Substrates" by Pomerantz (Box 360, Folder 2243)
  - "Studies on the Synthesis of Insulin by the Solid Phase Method" by Marglin, 1972 (Box 360, Folder 2244-2245, Box 361, Folder 2246)
  - "Studies on Von Willebrand Factor in Plasma and Urine, in Health and Disease"by Silveira, 1990 (Box 361, Folder 2247)
  - Strepogenin Reprints (Box 361, Folder 2248)
  - "A Study of Some Agents which Affect Cholinergic Transmission" by Beers, 1971 (Box 361, Folder 2249)
  - "Substrate Conformation and Hydrogen Bonding in the Active Sites of Protein Kinases" by Thomas, 1986 (Box 361, Folder 2250)
  - "Substrate Specificity of Calf Thymus Histone Deacetylase: Synthetic and Degradative Histone Peptides Active as Substrates for the Histone Deacetylase" by Krieger, 1976 (Box 362, Folder 2251-2252)
  - "Succinyl Phosphate and the Succinyl Coenzyme A Synthetase Reaction" by Hildebrand, 1969 (Box 362, Folder 2253)
  - Swain, PNAS (Box 363, Folder 2254)
  - Swain, PNAS (Box 363, Folder 2254A)
  - "Synthesis and Hormonal Activity of [Tyr22] Glucagon and [des His1, Tyr22] Glucagon" by Lu, Mojsov, and Merrifield (Box 363, Folder 2255)
  - Synthesis of Angiotensins by the Solid-Phase Method (Box 363, Folder 2256)
  - "Synthesis of a Cyclic Peptide" by Mitchell, 1969 (Box 363, Folder 2257)
  - "The Synthesis of an Enzyme" by Denkewalter and Hirshmann (Box 363, Folder 2258)
  - "The Synthesis of an Enzyme with the Sequence and Activity of Ribonuclease A" (Box 363, Folder 2259)
  - "The Synthesis of L-Seryl-L-Histidyl-L-Leucyl-L-Valyl-L-Glutamic Acid, a Peptide with Strepogenin Activity" by Merrifield and Woolley (Box 363, Folder 2260)
  - "The Synthesis of Ribonuclease A" by Gutte and Merrifield (Box 363, Folder 2261)
  - "Synthesis of Peptides with Strepogenin Activity" by Merrifield and Woolley (Box 364, Folder 2262)
  - "Synthesis of the Growth Factor L-Seryl-L-Histidyl-L-Leucyl-L-Valyl-L-Glutamic Acid" by Merrifield and Woolley (Box 364, Folder 2263)
  - Synthetic Antigens, NMR, 1999 (Box 364, Folder 2264)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Semisynthesis (Box 364, Folder 2265)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Stephen B. Kent, Related Papers (Box 364, Folder 2266)
  - Synthetic Antigens, Unlabeled Folder (Box 364, Folder 2267-2269)
  - "A Synthetic Approach to the Structure-Function Relationships in the Murine Epidermal Growth Factor Molecule" by Heath, 1986 (Box 365, Folder 2270)
  - Synthetic Efficiency Manuscript, Copies of Older Version (Box 365, Folder 2271)
  - "Synthetic Peptides VH(27-28) and VH(16-68) of the Myeloma Immunoglobulin M603 Heavy Chain and their Association with the Natural Light Chain to Form an Antigen Binding Site" by Kubiak, Whitney, and Merrifield (Box 365, Folder 2272)
  - T (Box 365, Folder 2273, Box 366, Folder 2274)
  - Tables from Emil (Kaiser), 1984 November 12 (Box 366, Folder 2275)
  - Tam, James (Box 366, Folder 2276)
    - A novel structure motif of antimicrobial particle..., 2016:FA415:009 (Box 366, Folder 2276)
  - Tam, James, AIDS Vaccine, PNAS, 1992 (Box 366, Folder 2277)
  - Tam, James, Cyclic Peptides (Box 366, Folder 2278)
  - Tam, James, Cyclic Peptides (Box 366, Folder 2278A)
  - Tam, James, "Orthogonal Ligation" (Box 366, Folder 2279)
  - Tam, James, PNAS (Box 367, Folder 2280)
  - Tam, James, PNAS (Box 367, Folder 2280A)
  - Tam, James, PNAS (Box 367, Folder 2281)
  - Tam, James, PNAS (Box 367, Folder 2281A)
  - Tam, James, TGF (Transforming Growth Factor) Physiology (Box 367, Folder 2282)
  - Tam and Lu, PNAS (Box 367, Folder 2283)
  - Tam and Lu, PNAS (Box 367, Folder 2283A)
  - Tam et al., TGF, PNAS, 1986 (Box 368, Folder 2284)
  - Tam, Todaro, TGF (Box 368, Folder 2285)
  - TFMSA ("Mechanisms of Benzyl Protecting Groups Removal in Synthetic Peptides by Trifluoromethanesulfonic Acid Trifluoroacetic Acid-Dimethylsulfice") (Box 368, Folder 2286)
  - U, V (Box 368, Folder 2287-2288)
  - Unfoldered Materials (Box 368, Folder 2289)
  - Unfoldered Reprints (Box 368, Folder 2290-2291, Box 369, Folder 2292-2295, Box 370, Folder 2296-2298, Box 371, Folder 2299-2302, Box 372, Folder 2303-2306, Box 373, Folder 2307-2309, Box 374, Folder 2310-2313, Box 375, Folder 2314-2317, Box 376, Folder 2318-2321, Box 377, Folder 2322-2325, Box 378, Folder 2326-2329)
  - Unfoldered Reprints and Citations (Box 378, Folder 2329)
  - Unlabeled Folder (Box 378, Folder 2330, Box 379, Folder 2331-2336, Box 380, Folder 2337-2341, Box 381, Folder 2342-2346, Box 382, Folder 2347-2351, Box 383, Folder 2352-2356, Box 384, Folder 2357-2361, Box 385, Folder 2362-2364)
    - Disk, 2016:FA415:010 (Box 379, Folder 2335)
  - Unlabeled Folder, Charts and Figures (Box 385, Folder 2365)
  - Unlabeled Illustrations (Box 385, Folder 2366, Box 386, Folder 2367-2368)
  - Unlabeled Reprints (Box 386, Folder 2369)
  - Unson (Box 386, Folder 2370)
  - Unson Serine Paper (Box 386, Folder 2371)
  - Van Rietschoten, PNAS (Box 387, Folder 2372)
  - Van Rietschoten, PNAS (Box 387, Folder 2372A)
  - W (Box 387, Folder 2373)
  - Wade, David (Box 387, Folder 2374)
  - Wang Manuscripts (Box 387, Folder 2375)
  - Wells (Box 387, Folder 2376)
  - Woolley Notebook, 1935-1938 (Box 387, Folder 2377)
  - Woolley Reprints (Box 387, Folder 2378, Box 388, Folder 2379-2382, Box 389, Folder 2383-2387)
  - Wnsch, Erich (Box 389, Folder 2388)
  - X, Y, Z (Box 389, Folder 2389)
  - Yajima RNase (Box 390, Folder 2390)
  - Zaslavsky (Box 390, Folder 2391)
  - Zasloff (Box 390, Folder 2392)
    - Disk, 2016:FA415:011 (Box 390, Folder 2392)
  - Zasloff (Box 390, Folder 2392A)
  - Zetterqvist, PNAS (Box 390, Folder 2393)
  - Zetterqvist, PNAS (Box 390, Folder 2393A)
  - Zaia, Dimas A.M. (Box 390, Folder 2394)
  - Zaia, Dimas A.M., VIP (Box 390, Folder 2395)
- Talks, Trips, and Commitments, Series 6
  - 2000-2001 (Box 390, Folder 2396)
  - 1st American Peptide Symposium, 1968 (Box 391, Folder 2397)
  - 2nd American Peptide Symposium (Box 391, Folder 2398)
  - 2nd Israeli-Polish Symposium on the Chemistry and Biology of Peptides and Proteins, Israel, 1995 (Box 391, Folder 2399)
  - 3rd American Peptide Symposium, 1972 (Box 391, Folder 2400)
  - 4th American Peptide Symposium, 1975 (Box 391, Folder 2401-2402)
  - 4th International Conference on Polymer Supported Reactions in Organic Chemistry, Prof. Josep Castells, Spain, 1988 (Box 391, Folder 2403)
  - 5th American Peptide Symposium, 1977 (Box 391, Folder 2404)
  - 6th American Peptide Symposium, 1979 (Box 392, Folder 2405)
  - 7th American Peptide Symposium, 1981 (Box 392, Folder 2406)
  - 7th Cyprus Conference on New Methods in Drug Research, 1996 (Box 392, Folder 2407)
  - Seventh International Congress of Biochemistry, Tokyo, 1967 (Box 392, Folder 2408)
  - 8th American Peptide Symposium, 1983 (Box 392, Folder 2409)
  - 8th European Peptide Symposium, 1966 (Box 392, Folder 2410)
  - 9th American Peptide Symposium, 1983 (Box 392, Folder 2411)
  - 9th European Peptide Symposium (Box 393, Folder 2412)
  - 10th American Peptide Symposium, 1987 May 23-29 (Box 393, Folder 2413)
  - 10th European Peptide Symposium (Box 393, Folder 2414)
  - 10th International Congress of Biochemistry, Hamburg, 1976 (Box 393, Folder 2415)
  - 11th American Peptide Symposium, 1989 (Box 393, Folder 2416)
  - 12th American Peptide Symposium, 1991 (Box 393, Folder 2417)
  - 13th American Peptide Symposium, 1993 (Box 393, Folder 2418)
  - 14th American Peptide Symposium, 1995 (Box 394, Folder 2419)
  - 15th American Peptide Symposium, 1997 (Box 394, Folder 2420)
  - 15th European Peptide Symposium, 1978 (Box 394, Folder 2421)
  - 16th American Peptide Symposium, 1999 June 26-July 1 (Box 394, Folder 2422)
  - 16th American Peptide Symposium, Perspectives Session, 1999 (Box 394, Folder 2423)
  - 16th European Peptide Symposium, 1980 (Box 394, Folder 2424)
  - 17th American Peptide Symposium, 2001 (Box 395, Folder 2425)
  - 17th European Peptide Symposium, 1982 (Box 395, Folder 2426)
  - 18th European Peptide Symposium, 1984 (Box 395, Folder 2427)
  - 19th European Peptide Symposium, Greece, 1986 August 31-September 5 (Box 395, Folder 2428)
  - 20th European Peptide Symposium, 1988 (Box 395, Folder 2429)
  - 20th North Eastern Regional Medicinal Chemistry and Pharmacognosy Meeting, Rhode Island, 1995 (Box 395, Folder 2430)
  - 21st European Peptide Symposium, 1990 (Box 395, Folder 2431)
  - 23rd European Peptide Symposium, 1994 (Box 395, Folder 2432)
  - 23rd International Congress of Pure and Applied Chemistry, 1971 (Box 395, Folder 2433)
  - 25th European Peptide Symposium, Budapest, 1998 August 30-September 4 (Box 395, Folder 2434)
  - 27th European Peptide Symposium, Sorrento, 2002 August 31-September 6 (Box 396, Folder 2435)
  - Abbott Laboratories, Sarin, 1985 November 24-25 (Box 396, Folder 2436)
  - ABRF (Association of Biomolecular Resource Facilities), 1998 March 12 (Box 396, Folder 2437)
  - ABRF (Association of Biomolecular Resource Facilities), Slides, Copies of Slides Submitted, 1988 March 6 (Box 396, Folder 2438)
  - Adelphi University, 1987 April 21 (Box 396, Folder 2439)
  - American Academy of Achievement, Golden Plate Award, 1985 June 27-29 (Box 396, Folder 2440)
  - American Chemical Society, 18th Central Regional Meeting, 1986 June 1-5 (Box 396, Folder 2441)
  - American Chemical Society, Chicago Section, 1977 (Box 396, Folder 2442)
  - American Chemical Society, Chicago Section Meeting, 1988 (Box 396, Folder 2443)
  - American Chemical Society, Hirschmann Award in Peptide Chemistry, Massachusetts, 1990 (Box 396, Folder 2444)
  - American Chemical Society, Leo J. Friend Award Symposium, Louisiana, 1996 (Box 396, Folder 2445)
  - American Chemical Society meeting, Symposium, Gutte (Box 396, Folder 2446)
  - American Chemical Society, Semi-Annual Research Conference, Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1977 (Box 396, Folder 2447)
  - American Chemical Society, Staten Island, 1974 (Box 396, Folder 2448)
  - American Chemical Society Symposium, "Biopolymers: Advances in the Chemistry and Biology of Peptides and Proteins," Chicago, 1975 (Box 396, Folder 2449)
  - American Institute of Chemists, 1985 May 23 (Box 397, Folder 2450)
  - American Institute of Chemists, Chemical Pioneer Award, New Jersey, 1993 (Box 397, Folder 2451)
  - American Peptide Society (Box 397, Folder 2452)
  - Amoco Research Center, Royer, 1985 November 26 (Box 397, Folder 2453)
  - Barcelona, 1986 September 22-27 (Box 397, Folder 2454)
  - Beckman-Rockefeller University Symposium, 1985 April 12 (Box 397, Folder 2455)
  - Big Brothers, Inc. Awards Dinner, New York, New York, 1988 (Box 397, Folder 2456)
  - Bogota, 1984 November 5 (Box 397, Folder 2457)
  - Boston College, Dr. Moran, 1984 May 21 (Box 397, Folder 2458)
  - Boston Peptide Club, Figures for Lecture, Cecropin A(1-33), 1982 (Box 397, Folder 2459)
  - Boston Talk and Poster (Box 397, Folder 2460)
  - British Polymer Journal, Vol. 16, No. 4, 1984 (Box 397, Folder 2461)
  - Brooklyn College, Sigma Xi, 1986 April 10 (Box 397, Folder 2462)
  - Budapest, 1987 August 10-14 (Box 397, Folder 2463)
  - California School Boards Foundation's Public Education Hall of Fame Induction, 1991 (Box 398, Folder 2464)
  - Cambridge Meeting, Roche, 1971 (Box 398, Folder 2465)
  - Canadian Biochemical Society Symposium, 1974 (Box 398, Folder 2466)
  - Centenary Lectures, 1987 February-March (Box 398, Folder 2467)
  - Chemical and Engineering News, Boston, 1998 August 23 (Box 398, Folder 2468)
  - Chemical Landmark Symposium, 2000 (Box 398, Folder 2469)
  - China, 1984 May-June (Box 398, Folder 2470)
  - Chinese Peptide Symposium, Award Committee, 1996 (Box 398, Folder 2471)
  - CIBA Foundation Symposium No. 186, "Antimicrobial Peptides," England, 1994 (Box 399, Folder 2472)
  - The College of Staten Island, Katzir Symposium, New York, 1995 (Box 399, Folder 2473)
  - Committee on Synthesis of Medically Important Proteins, 1972-1973 (Box 399, Folder 2474)
  - Convocation, 1985 June 13 (Box 399, Folder 2475)
  - Dinner with Donors, 1985 September 17 (Box 399, Folder 2476)
  - Drew University, 1987 April 6 (Box 399, Folder 2477)
  - Edison Lecture, 1985 February 12 (Box 399, Folder 2478)
  - EUCHEM Conference, Prof. R. Jacquier, France, 1988 (Box 399, Folder 2479)
  - "An Evening at The Rockefeller University", 1988 (Box 399, Folder 2480)
  - Exeter Chemical Society Meeting, 1967 (Box 399, Folder 2481)
  - Faculty Committee on Biochemistry and Organic Chemistry (Box 399, Folder 2482)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson, 1985 February 21 (Box 399, Folder 2483)
  - Fort Collins Symposium, 1987 June 16 (Box 400, Folder 2484)
  - Founders Ball, 1987 May 5 (Box 400, Folder 2485)
  - "The Future of Antibodies in Human Diagnosis and Therapy," Symposium, Rockefeller University, 1975 (Box 400, Folder 2486)
  - Gooch-Stephens Lectures, Baylor, Waco, 1986 December 3-4 (Box 400, Folder 2487)
  - Gordon Conference, 1969 (Box 400, Folder 2488)
  - Gordon Conference, 1980 (Box 400, Folder 2489)
  - Gordon Conference, 1986 February 3-7 (Box 400, Folder 2490)
  - Gordon Conference on Peptides, Ventura, California, 1988 (Box 400, Folder 2491)
  - Gordon Conference, Proteins, 1966 (Box 400, Folder 2492)
  - Haber, Edgar, Program Project Grant and Site Visit, 1975-1977 (Box 400, Folder 2493)
  - Harden Conference and Liverpool Chemical Society Meeting (Box 401, Folder 2494)
  - Honorary Doctorate, Delaware Valley College, 1991 (Box 401, Folder 2495)
  - Honorary Doctorate, The Scripps Research Instiutte, 1998 (Box 401, Folder 2496)
  - House Committee - Merrifield, 1985 May 14 (Box 401, Folder 2497)
  - House Committee on Science and Technology, My (Merrifield) Testimony, 1985 February (Box 401, Folder 2498)
  - House Committee Testimony, 1985 (Box 401, Folder 2499)
  - Indiana University, 1980 (Box 401, Folder 2500)
  - International Symposium on Biologically Active Proteins and Peptides, Taiwan, 1988 (Box 401, Folder 2501)
  - International Symposium on Natural Products in Chemistry, Pakistan (Box 401, Folder 2502)
  - ISCO Award, University of Nebraska-Lincoln, 1977 (Box 401, Folder 2503)
  - Israel Meeting, 1987 August 16-21 (Box 402, Folder 2504)
  - Jaime I Prize Jury, 1998 July 5-7 (Box 402, Folder 2505)
  - Lab Seminar (Glucagon), 1985 February 19 (Box 402, Folder 2506)
  - Lancaster, 1984 July 3-5 (Box 402, Folder 2507)
  - Laurentian Hormone Conference, 1966 (Box 402, Folder 2508)
  - Lederle (Laboratories), 1985 May 15 (Box 402, Folder 2509)
  - List of Engagements, 1984-1995 (Box 402, Folder 2510)
  - Liverpool, 1980 (Box 402, Folder 2511)
  - Louisville, 1966 October 27 (Box 402, Folder 2512)
  - Louisville, 1986 February 17-19 (Box 402, Folder 2513)
  - Lunch Seminar Xeroxes (Box 402, Folder 2514)
  - Manhattan and Ramapo College Speeches (Box 402, Folder 2515)
  - Manhattan College, Ramapo College, 1999 April 23 (Box 402, Folder 2516)
  - Mark, Hermann F., 95th Birthday Symposium, 1990 (Box 402, Folder 2517)
  - Mark Symposium, 1985 May 6-7 (Box 403, Folder 2518)
  - Mayor Koch Reception (Box 403, Folder 2519)
  - Medical College of Ohio, 1972 (Box 403, Folder 2520)
  - Medical College of Virginia - Virginia Commonwealth University, Innovators of Biochemistry Award Lecture, 1988 (Box 403, Folder 2521)
  - Merrifield Party, 1989 (Box 403, Folder 2522)
  - Miami Symposium, 1968 (Box 403, Folder 2523)
  - Miles Laboratory Symposium, 1969 June 2-3 (Box 403, Folder 2524)
  - MIT (Massachusetts Institute of Technology) Site Visit, 1975 (Box 403, Folder 2525)
  - Modern Applications of Column Chromatography, University of Wisconsin, 1966 (Box 403, Folder 2526)
  - Molecular Basis of Membrane Function, Duke, 1968 August 20-23 (Box 403, Folder 2527)
  - Montebello High School, 2001 (Box 403, Folder 2528)
  - Moscow, 1984 June 19-23 (Box 403, Folder 2529)
  - Museum of Science and Industry, 1985 April 3 (Box 403, Folder 2530)
  - Natick Conference, 1968 October 8-9 (Box 403, Folder 2531)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1987 April 26 (Box 403, Folder 2532)
  - National Academy of Sciences Meeting, 1986 April 29 (Box 404, Folder 2533)
  - National Historic Landmark Symposium (Box 404, Folder 2534)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1980 (Box 404, Folder 2535)
  - National Institutes of Health, 1980 (Box 404, Folder 2535A)
  - National Science Foundation, Community College Day, 2001 April 26 (Box 404, Folder 2536)
  - New York Academy of Sciences, 1980 (Box 404, Folder 2537)
  - Newark College of Engineering, 1973 (Box 404, Folder 2538)
  - Nichols Medal (Box 404, Folder 2539)
  - Novel Anniversary Dinner, Hilton, 1986 December 9 (Box 404, Folder 2540)
  - Nobel Jubilee, 1991 December 5-11 (Box 404, Folder 2541)
  - Nobel Lecture, 1984 (Box 404, Folder 2542, Box 405, Folder 2543)
  - Orientation Lecture (Box 405, Folder 2544)
  - Ortho Pharmaceutical Corporation, Heavner, 1987 November 16-18 (Box 405, Folder 2545)
  - Oxford Meeting, Epton, 1986 September 15 (Box 405, Folder 2546)
  - Pan American Chemical Congress, 1985 October 13-19 (Box 405, Folder 2547)
  - Peptide Seminar Series (Box 405, Folder 2548)
  - Pierce Award (Box 405, Folder 2549)
  - Pisano Lecture, National Institutes of Health, 1986 March 26 (Box 405, Folder 2550)
  - Polymer Research Institute, Amherst, 1975 (Box 405, Folder 2551)
  - Porath Seminar, 1986 April 3 (Box 405, Folder 2552)
  - Press Conference, 1969 January 16 (Box 405, Folder 2553)
  - Protein Structure and Function, Alpine Inn, 1969 March 2-7 (Box 405, Folder 2554)
  - Radioactive Peptide Program, 1966-1967 (Box 405, Folder 2555)
  - "Rey Jaime I Prize in Science" Jury, Spain, 1991 (Box 406, Folder 2556)
  - Ringberg Conference to Celebrate Erich Wntsch's 70th Birthday, Germany, 1993 (Box 406, Folder 2557)
  - Rio Lecture Tour, 1974 (Box 406, Folder 2558)
  - Roche Consult, 1991 October 22 (Box 406, Folder 2559)
  - Roche Meeting, 1990 May 3 (Box 406, Folder 2560)
  - Rockefeller Dinner, 1985 May 20 (Box 406, Folder 2561)
  - Rockefeller University Administrator Meeting, 1985 March 29 (Box 406, Folder 2562)
  - Rockefeller University Commencement, 1998 June 10-11 (Box 406, Folder 2563)
  - Rockefeller University, Lab Seminars, Cecropin A (Box 406, Folder 2564)
  - Rockefeller University, Trust and Estate Gift Plans Committee, 1986 January 30 (Box 406, Folder 2565)
  - Round Table UCLAF on Brain Oligopeptides (Box 406, Folder 2566)
  - Roussel-UCLAF Round Table, "Polymer Bound Molecules", 1976 (Box 407, Folder 2567)
  - Rutgers, 1987 November 2-3 (Box 407, Folder 2568)
  - Rutgers University, Merck Lecture, 1991 (Box 407, Folder 2569)
  - Salk Institute, 1986 April 17 (Box 407, Folder 2570)
  - Seminars in Polypeptide Biochemistry (Box 407, Folder 2571)
  - The Smithsonian Associates Lecture, "Nobel Laureates in Science", 1995 (Box 407, Folder 2572)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Donation of Peptide Synthesizer and Loan of Nobel Prize Certificate, 1984-1990 (Box 407, Folder 2573)
  - Socit de Chimie Industrielle - American Section - Luncheon Meeting, New York, 1994 (Box 407, Folder 2574)
  - Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis Talks (Box 407, Folder 2575)
  - Spain, 1974-1975 (Box 407, Folder 2576)
  - Staff Meeting, "Isolation and Synthesis of Peptides with Strepogenin Activity" (Box 407, Folder 2577)
  - Staff Meeting, Solid Phase Peptide Synthesis, 1964 (Box 407, Folder 2578)
  - Staff Meeting, "Specificity of Biologically Active Peptides" (Box 407, Folder 2579)
  - SUNY Buffalo, 1985 November 2 (Box 407, Folder 2580)
  - Swarthmore, 1986 March 21 (Box 407, Folder 2581)
  - Symposia and Conferences in Japan, 1988-1989 (Box 407, Folder 2582)
  - Symposia and Conferences in Japan, 1992 (Box 408, Folder 2583)
  - Symposia and Lectures in China, 1992-1994 (Box 408, Folder 2584)
  - Symposium on the Occasion of the 70th Birthday of Ralph F. Hirschmann, University of Pennsylvania, 1971 (Box 408, Folder 2585)
  - Symposium on "The Role of Chemical Science and Technology in the Society of the 21st Century," Spain, 1995 (Box 408, Folder 2586)
  - Texas A&M, Scott, 1986 December 1-3 (Box 408, Folder 2587)
  - Texas Tech Visiting Lecturer, Lubbock, Texas, 1988 (Box 408, Folder 2588)
  - Troy, 1980 (Box 408, Folder 2589)
  - UCLA, 1974 (Box 408, Folder 2590)
  - UCLA, 1980 (Box 408, Folder 2591)
  - UCLA, 1985 May 29 (Box 409, Folder 2592)
  - UCLA, 1986 (Box 409, Folder 2593)
  - UCLA, 1986 June 21-22 (Box 409, Folder 2594)
  - UCLA, Clarke, 1985 May 29 (Box 409, Folder 2595)
  - UCLA Colloquium, "Synthetic Peptides: Approaches to Biological Problems," Park City, Utah, 1988 (Box 409, Folder 2596)
  - UCLA Edward A. Dickson Alumnus of the Year, California, 1997 (Box 409, Folder 2597)
  - UCLA Seaborg Medal and Dedication of New Molecular Science Building, 1993 (Box 409, Folder 2598)
  - UCLA Symposia on Molecular and Cellular Biology, Colorado, 1990 (Box 409, Folder 2599)
  - UCLA Symposium, 1987 April 4-11 (Box 409, Folder 2600)
  - University of Delaware, 1976 (Box 409, Folder 2601)
  - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey, 1985 May 22 (Box 409, Folder 2602)
  - University of Missouri, 1986 April 22 (Box 409, Folder 2603)
  - University of North Carolina, 1987 April 10-11 (Box 409, Folder 2604)
  - University of Ottawa, Frechet, 1985 November 10-12 (Box 409, Folder 2605)
  - University of South Florida, Castle Lecture Series, 1987 November 12-14 (Box 409, Folder 2606)
  - University of Wisconsin, Peptide Symposium, 1973 (Box 410, Folder 2607)
  - University of Wyoming, 1986 June 24 (Box 410, Folder 2608)
  - USSR, 1974 (Box 410, Folder 2609)
  - Venable LEcture, 1972-1973 (Box 410, Folder 2610)
  - Washington University (St. Louis) School of Medicine, 20th Annual Oliver H. Lowry Lecture, 1998 (Box 410, Folder 2611)
  - Weizmann Dinner, 1985 October 20 (Box 410, Folder 2612)
  - West Virginia University, 1976 (Box 410, Folder 2613)
  - White House, NAS, NIH (National Academy of Sciences, National Institutes of Health), 1985 February 11 (Box 410, Folder 2614)
  - William Paterson College "Chemistry Day" Keynote Speaker, New Jersey, 1995 (Box 410, Folder 2615)
  - Wnsch, Erich, Max Planck Institute of Biochemistry, 1987 (Box 410, Folder 2616)
- Audio-Visual and Oversized Materials, 7
  - Adenyl Cylase (Box 411, Folder 2617)
  - Automated Synthesis of Peptides, 1965 (Box 411, Folder 2618)
  - Cecropin (Box 411, Folder 2619)
  - Glucagon (Box 411, Folder 2620)
  - Nucleotide Problem, 1952 (Box 411, Folder 2621)
  - The Peptides, Barany and Merrifield (Box 411, Folder 2622)
  - Solid Phase Synthesis of Angiotensinyl-Bradykinin, 1964 (Box 411, Folder 2623)
  - Strepogenin (Box 411, Folder 2624)
  - Unlabeled Illustrations (Box 411, Folder 2625)
  - Tapes and CD (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - VHS tape, "The Rockefeller University and The American Peptide Institute: 'Peptide and Protein Synthesis: Origin and Development'", 2016:FA415:012 (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - Betacam tape, "Peptide and Protein Synthesis: Origin and Development", 2016:FA415:013 (Box 411, Folder 2626)
    - Cassette tape, "1984 Merrifield's Nobel Prize Press Conference, David Rockefeller Remarks", 2016:FA415:014 (Box 411, Folder 2626)